freedomhacker.net 2015-09-04

# Privacy Policy - Freedom Hacker

**Privacy Policy for FreedomHacker.net**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please email us at author [at]freedomhacker.net.

At freedomhacker.net the privacy of our visitors is extremely important to us. This privacy policy outlines what personal data we collect and how me may utilize this data.

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, freedomhacker.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

Google Adsense  
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on freedomhacker.net send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

freedomhacker.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. freedomhacker.net’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

Affiliate Disclosure 

We are a professional review site that receives compensation from the companies whose products we review. We test each product thoroughly and give trusted ratings on companies we’ve vetted. We are independently owned and the opinions expressed here are our own.
